

Applicant for:

[Remote] Senior Software Developer (.NET, ReactJS)

Futurify 28 March 2024

Lương Văn Triệu

☑ trieulv262@gmail.com

Main interests: .NET, C#

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Hi There,

I'm a skilled and experienced Senior Software Engineer with over 8 years of design and maintenance software within the Microsoft framework. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies to enhance my capabilities and performance. I always seek a dynamic working environment, new challenges, and opportunities to showcase my skills and creativity.

Thank.

[&]quot;Hiring the wrong person is the most costly mistake you can make." - Brian Tracy

LUONG VAN TRIEU

Senior Software Engineer





I'm a skilled and experienced Senior Software Engineer with over 8 years of design and maintenance software within the Microsoft framework. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies to enhance my capabilities and performance. I always seek a dynamic working environment, new challenges, and opportunities to showcase my skills and creativity.

If you are interested in working with me or learning more about me, please feel free to contact me anytime.

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

- .NET C#
- ASP.NET MVC
- ASP.NET Core
- WPF

Cloud Services:

- Azure Fundamentals
- Azure Functions

Database: SQL Server

Project Methodology: Agile

Microservices:

- Development and architecture of microservices
- API design and implementation
- Restful API development
- Swagger documentation

Design Patterns and Principles:

- Knowledge of design patterns
- IoC (Inversion of Control)
- Dependency Injection (DI)
- SOLID principles

Testing:

- Unit Testing
- Test-Driven Development (TDD)

Front-End Technologies:

 HTML - CSS - Bootstrap - Javascript jQuery

Front-End Frameworks:

• Basic with React - Angular - Vue.js

Source Control: TFS - GIT- Azure DevOps

WORK HISTORY

APERIA SOLUTIONS VIETNAM CO LTD

Leader/Senior Software Engineer | 2020 - Present

Responsibilities:

- Developing and maintaining software solutions catering to the fintech industry.
- Collaborated with various teams to gather and clarify tasks and distributed tasks to meet the sprint goals and dateline of the project.
- Worked closely with Technical Architecture to design and implement complex features. Implemented microservices architecture.

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, MSSQL, Microservice, API, WPF, Azure DevOps, CICD

Project Methodology: Agile

GOODLAND INFORMATICS

Senior Software Engineer | 2018 - 2020

Responsibilities:

- Key contributor as a Senior Software Engineer in the development and maintenance of Content Management Systems (CMS) within the company, ensuring the stability, scalability, and security of CMS systems.
- Optimizing performance and user experience.

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET MVC, MSSQL, API, and OAuth

Project Methodology: Agile

VACS TECHNOLOGY

Software Developer | 2016 - 2018

Responsibilities:

- Contributed significantly to the development and maintenance of Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) and Accounting Management Systems (AMS).
- Collaborated with the team to enhance functionalities, improve system performance, and ensure data integrity within ERP and AMS applications.

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET MVC, and MSSQL

TINH VAN CONSULTING

Software Developer | 2015

Responsibilities: Development and maintenance of web applications, contributing to the company's software portfolio.

Technologies: Visual Basic (VB) and Oracle technologies

EMSVN JSC Software Developer | 2015

Responsibilities: Contributed significantly as a .NET Developer in the development and maintenance of websites. Collaborated with the development team to ensure the stability, performance, and security of the websites.

Technologies: C#, ASP.NET, and MSSQL

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aperia project - Interaction Management

Client: Fiserv customer

Role: Technical Team Lead | 2021 - Present

Responsibilities: As the Technical Lead for the Interaction Management project, I collaborated with various teams to gather and clarify tasks and distributed tasks to meet the sprint goals and dateline of the project.

Designed and implemented a task management system that automatically creates tasks for relevant issues, facilitating prompt resolution by the appropriate support team. Implemented microservices architecture.

Technologies an Tools: ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, WPF, JWT OAuth, Restful API, NUnit | MSSQL | CI/CD | HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery

Version Control: Azure DevOps, GIT, TFS

Project Methodology: Agile

Aperia project - Heatmap

Client: US customer

Role: Senior Software Engineer | 2020

Responsibilities: Worked closely with Business Analysts to gain a comprehensive understanding of project requirements, contributing to the project's modular and scalable architecture. Successfully handled the implementation of US-Map functionality, enhancing geographical data representation within the application.

Technologies: ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Core, JWT OAuth, Restful API | MSSQL | HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery

Version Control: Azure DevOps, GIT, TFS

Project Methodology: Agile

Petron Malaysia Customers Portal

Client: Malaysia Customers

Role: Senior Software Engineer | 2019 - 2020

Responsibilities: Worked closely with the Technical Lead to understand project goals and objectives, ensuring a clear understanding of assigned tasks and aligning development efforts with project requirements.

Contributing to the development of robust and scalable solutions. Utilized my expertise in designing and implementing APIs to enhance the functionality and interoperability of the project.

Technologies: ASP.NET Core, Restful API | MSSQL | Reactjs

Version Control: GIT

Project Methodology: Agile

Content Management System

Client: Charity Advantage, US

Role: Software Engineer | 2018 - 2019

Responsibilities: Development of Content Management System (CMS) websites, encompassing the creation of websites, data management tools, a page builder, form builder, and campaign management functionalities.

Developed an intuitive page builder and form builder, empowering clients to easily create and manage web content without technical expertise.

Technologies: ASP.NET WebForm, ASP.NET MVC, Restful API | MSSQL | HTMS, CSS, JavaScript, Ajax, Bootstrap

Version Control: SVN

Project Methodology: Waterfall

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Technology (2009 - 2013)

Ho Chi Minh City Industry And Trade College

.NET Developer (2013 - 2014)

Nhat Nghe Education JSC

Web Developer (2012)

Nhat Nghe Education JSC